realeflow.com 2013-03-19

# 

                                        PRIVACY POLICY
We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.
Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet as
enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the Internet's vast array of
information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.
We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate Realeflow’s commitment to privacy and
security. This Privacy Policy describes how our company collects information from all end users
of our Internet services (the "Services")-those who access some of our Services but do not have
accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who may purchase Products and/or pay a monthly service
fee to subscribe to the Service ("Members")-what we do with the information we collect, and the
choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of such information.
Personal Information Our Company Collects and How It Is Used
Introduction. Our company collects information in different ways from Visitors and Members
who access the various parts of our Services and the network of Web sites accessible through our
Service. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our
Products and Services, and generally, do not share this information with third parties. However,
we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand
or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law
or other special cases described below.
Registration: Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up
for our Products or Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information
(such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the
Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is
used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). This information is not
shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances.
However, in instances where our company and a partner jointly promote our Services, we may
provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and username of
persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of
allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion.
In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. We
may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members
provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members). As
explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to
sell advertisements that appear on the Services.
Our Company Partners and Sponsors: Some products and services may be offered to Visitors
and Members in conjunction with an affiliate, independent contractor seller or non-affiliated
partner. To provide Visitors and Members some of these products and services, the partner may
need to collect and maintain personal information. In these instances, you will be notified before

any such data is collected or transferred and may decide not to use that particular service or
feature.
Additionally, our partners may have advertisements or co-branded Web Pages that are
cosponsored by an affiliate, independent contractor seller, or non-affiliated partner. Our company
may share non-identifying and aggregate information (except as described above), but not
personal information, with such partners in order to administer the co-branded products or
services offered.
Online Shopping: At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register to
receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or new product and service updates. In many
cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email
address, phone number, and credit/debit card information.
If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent directly to a
recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the recipient's
name, address, and phone number. Our company has no control over the third parties' use of any
personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing
so.
If you order services or products directly from our company we will use the personal information
you provide only to process that order. We do not share this information with outside parties
except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
Online Advertisements: Our company may display our online advertisements. In those cases we
share aggregated and non-identifying information about our Visitors and Members collected
through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with these
advertisers.
Additionally, in some instances, we use this aggregated and non-identifying information to
deliver tailored advertisements or joint ventures. For instance, an advertiser or joint venture
company tells us the audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement tailored to the
audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we
may then display or send the advertisement to the intended audience. Our company does not
share personal information about its Visitors or Members with these advertisers or joint venture
companies.
Responses to Email Inquiries: When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to our company,
the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Our company does not
use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address
with any third party.
Voluntary Customer Surveys: We may periodically conduct both business and individual
customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they
provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of products and services
we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain

strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our
customer surveys is voluntary.
We may take the information we receive from individuals responding to our Customer Surveys
and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other customers we may have, to create
broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies,
education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the
aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new
services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared
with third parties.
Special Cases: It is our company's policy not to use or share the personal information about
Visitors or Members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you
an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
However, we may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information
regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason
if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: credit agencies,
collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law enforcement, or to satisfy laws, such as the
Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act, regulations, or
governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to
identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable
Use Policy or Terms Of Service, or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to
protect our company and our Members.
"Cookies" and How Our Company Uses Them. A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed
on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. Our company may use cookies to collect,
store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and
services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks.
If you are a Visitor or Member we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide
customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any
of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit other Web sites where you
are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies.
Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies
and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.
Our Company Commitment to Children's Privacy. Protecting children's privacy is especially
important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of
1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore we restrict our Web site to persons eighteen years
or older.
YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF
YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO
ACCESS THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR

USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS
WITHIN THE CHILD ONLINE PRIVACY ACT (COPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS
DOING SO.
Public Forums: Please remember that any information you may disclose in any Member
Directory, or other public areas of our Web sites or the Internet, becomes public information.
You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public
areas.
Our Company's Commitment to Data Security: Services and Web sites we sponsor have security
measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we
cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally
obtaining this information.
Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy: If you have any questions about this
Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us through the contact
information provided on this Web site.
Revisions to This Policy: Our company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy,
our Terms Of Service agreement, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any
manner, by updating this posting. Your use of this site after such changes are implemented
constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of these changes. Please consult this privacy
statement prior to every use for any changes.
Last updated: November 13, 2007
